http://www.ohiodominican.edu/home/privacy-policy

Update Browser
You are running an old version of Android
This site was optimized for modern browsers. Please consider updating your version of Android if able.
Update Browser
Your version of Internet Explorer is Outdated
This site has been optimized for modern browsers. Please consider either updating to the latest version of Internet Explorer, or consider viewing the site in Chrome or Firefox.
Navigate to:
Home
Request Info
Apply Now
Visit
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Information you provide to us: Any information that you provide to us through an Ohio Dominican University website, such as your email address, name, or phone number, will be held with the utmost care. Your information may be used for official University business; to communicate with you regarding promotional offers, new products, and other information that we think may be interesting to you; or we may redirect your inquiry or comment to another department in the university to respond appropriately.  Information we collect automatically: This website uses cookies to collect information about your computer, including IP address, operating system and browser type. We do not collect any personally identifiable information, and we cannot identify you based on this information. By using this website, you agree to Ohio Dominican University’s use of cookies for tracking and statistical data purposes.  About retargeting: We work with third-party companies to collect information about our website usage in order to increase the effectiveness of our marketing. Recorded data is aggregated and shared with us. No personally identifiable information is collected or shared.  Contacting us: If you have any questions about ODU’s website privacy policy or the practices of this website, you may contact: Ohio Dominican University
Office of Marketing & Public Relations
614-251-4576 marketing@ohiodominican.edu
